

# THAI THI YEN NHI Front-end Developer

nhithai88@gmail.com +84 974 833 783 nhidev.netlify.com

With a strong technical skill-set, attention to detail, and 4+ years of experience, I want to work as a front-end web developer where I could create digital magic and elevate user experience to the next level.

### Experience

REDWEB

Front-end Developer

09/2017 - 06/2018

- Create, modify websites for Joomla CMS and our ecommerce platform.
- Upgrade client sites (ecommerce platform, Joomla CMS).
- Fix front end related bugs that were identified in QA, beta and production environments.
- Attend wire frame review, design and html code walkthrough meetings.

1PAC

Front-end Developer

08/2016 - 06/2017 1pac.vn

- Develop HTML/CSS templates from Photoshop visual design and wireframes.
- Refactor code and delivering products with high quality, write code that runs cross browsers.
- Research trending technologies and apply it to real production.

#### CANON LE BAO MINH

Web Developer

05/2014 - 07/2016 lebaominh.vn

- Create, modify websites for WordPress CMS.
- Used jquery to build accordion style content, drag and drop functionality, calendar, popup and modal windows
- Cross-browser compatible by writing W3C validated Semantic XHTML.
- Responsible for solving page layout issues.
- Monitored the web analysis reports to view the performance of the company websites.

#### Skills

HTML	CSS	SCSS	JavaScript	Bootstrap	jC	uery	ReactJS	Grunt
Joomla	Wor	dpress	Photoshop	Github	Jira			

#### Education

Bachelor of Science from Hutech University (2013)

Associate of Science from Hoa Sen University (2009)

## Language

English (intermediate)